原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     小酸奶  余欢  Sakura的小书包
翻译     DerbyNinja  闲汀
翻译     盐湖凉开水  布塔
纽约州北部
时间轴    西·查  紫夏  caroline
校对     雷霆布塔
后期     渔夫
别指望了
总监     布塔
萨德
Thad...
我说了不许带玩具去爷爷家
I said no toys at Grandfather's.
但今天是圣诞节
But it's Christmas.
住手
Stop it!
爸爸
Hey, Dad!
萨德  你不能总是找别人哭诉
Thad, you can't go crying to other people all the time.
男人需要知道什么时候该捍卫自己
A man needs to know when to stand up for himself.
亲爱的魔法不是真的球
Dear Magic-Isn't-Real Ball,
萨德会长大成男人吗
will Thad ever be a man?
扎心
Ouch.
"前景不理想"
"Outlook not so good."
你弄坏了
You broke it.
爸爸  希德
Dad? Sid?
谁来救救我
Someone help me!
救命
Help!
有人吗
Hello?
萨德斯
Thaddeus.
萨德斯·希瓦那
Thaddeus Sivana.
你是谁
Who are you?
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?
我是巫师议会的最后一位成员
I am the last of the Council of Wizards.
发誓要保护王国免受七宗罪的危害
Sworn to protect the realms from the Seven Deadly Sins.
但是年复一年
But years have passed,
我日渐虚弱
and I grow weak.
所以我在寻找一名继承者
That is why I seek a champion
来继承我的魔法
to inherit my magic.
你想让我施法吗
You want me to do magic?
只要有这个
With this,
我的力量都将归你所有
all of my powers will become yours.
但是首先
But first...
你必须证明你拥有至纯之心
you must demonstrate that you're pure of heart
和强韧的精神
and strong in spirit.
他撒谎
He lies.
别做他的继承者
Don't be his champion.
我们可以给你力量
We can give you power.
拿走眼睛
Take the eye.
拿走
Take it.
你父亲觉得你软弱
Your father thinks you're weak.
让他看看你的力量
Show him your power.
拿走眼睛
Take the eye.
不
No!
怎么  怎么回事
What? What happened?
只有至纯之心才能抵挡住他们的诱惑
Only the purest of hearts can resist their temptations.
但是你
But you,
你永远不配
you will never be worthy.
等等
Wait.
-我可以的  我发誓  -什么
- I'm good enough, I swear! - What?
让我回去
Let me back in!
冷静点  萨德
Calm down, Thad!
不要开门  住手
Don't open the door! Stop it!
-冷静点  -别闹了
- Calm down. - Stop!
我要杀了你  你这个小疯子
I'm gonna kill you, you little freak!
别...
Stop...
我刚刚还在那里
I... I was just there.
-那男人  那巫师带我进了一座城堡  -住口
- This man, this wizard, he took me to a castle and... - Stop.
住口  给我住口
Stop! Stop it!
你这个可怜可悲的小混蛋
You miserable, whiny, little shit!
你差点害死我们
You could have killed us!
你明白吗
Do you understand that?
爸爸
Dad?
Dad!
爸爸
Dad?
你没事的
You're okay.
你不会有事的
You're gonna be okay.
都是你干的
You did this.
You did this!
不  爸爸
No. Dad.
来找我们
你的魔法越来越弱
Your magic grows weak.
很快你就无法压制我们了
Soon, you won't be able to contain us.
寻觅咒
Seeking Spell,
为我找寻值得拥有力量的人
find me one soul who is worthy.
不管需要花多久
No matter how long it takes.
雷霆沙赞!
费城
如今
毕舍普典当铺
天哪  警察叔叔
Holy moly! The boys in blue!
见到你们真是太好了
Sure glad to see you.
我一看到就报警了
I called as soon as I saw.
他们在里面
They're in there.
待在这儿
You stay here.
便利店  典当铺  拳击馆
警察
Police!
我看到他们躲在里面
I saw 'em hide back in there.
借贷
-警察  我们要进来了  -警察
- Police, coming in! - Police!
-这里没人  -什么意思
- There's nobody here. - What do you mean?
-这是个橱柜  -你们还真信啊
- It's a closet. - You really bought that, huh?
不不不
No, no, no!
住手  住手  住手
Stop, stop, stop!
赶紧打开  小子
Open this up right now, kid.
这是联邦重罪  小子  你不能这么做
That's a federal offense, kid. You can't do that!
不要上那辆车
Do not go in that car.
快点把门打开  拜托
Come on, open the door. Please.
拜托了
Please, come on.
快点打开
Open this, right now!
很好  很好笑
Very good, very funny.
很好笑  太好了  真好笑
Very funny. That's great. That's hilarious.
姓名  蕾切尔·M·巴特森
地址  霍夫曼街21号
城市  费城
霍夫曼街21号
调度中心  劳尔伍德商业中心需要增援
Dispatch, we need backup at the Laurelwood shopping center, please.
调度中心  取消请求
Dispatch, cancel that request.
有个小子偷了我们的对讲机
Some kid stole our walkie-talkies.
对讲机  你几岁啊
Walkie-talkies? How old are you?
吉诺牛排
不不不
No, no, no.
那是我的午餐  小子
That's my lunch, kid!
巴特森小姐
Miss Batson...
我一直在找你
I've been looking for you.
不  天啊
No. Gosh.
是我  比利
It's me. It's Billy.
好了
Okay.
孩子永远能射中  每次都能射中
我想要那只老虎
I want the tiger.
我知道  亲爱的  但妈妈并不擅长这个
I know, honey, I know. But Mom's not exactly going pro here.
我们射中了一个
We got one!
但我想要一只老虎
But I wanted a tiger.
但这才是真正的大奖  宝贝  看
But this is the real prize, baby. See?
这可以让你受用一生
You can use that your whole life.
你总是能找到你要走的路
You'll always find your way.
我不能弄丢那个球
I can't let the ball get away.
妈妈
Mom?
Mom!
妈妈
你跟谁一起来的  小家伙
Who are you with, bud?
他说他叫比利·巴特森
Yeah, he says it's Billy Batson.
别担心  孩子
Don't worry, kid.
她肯定很快就会来找你的
I'm sure she'll come looking before too long, okay?
父母一定会来的
They always do.
妈妈  我回家了
Mom, I'm home.
哪位
Yes?
你是蕾切尔·巴特森吗
Yeah, uh, is this Rachel Batson?
谁啊
Who's asking?
实际上...
Yeah, see, the thing is...
我觉得你是我妈妈
I think you're my mom.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
抱歉打扰了
Sorry to bother you.
非得拿走我的午餐是吧
Just had to take my lunch, huh?
给我留了点薯条吗
You save me any fries?
E·B·格洛弗
匹兹堡的寄养家庭两周前上报你失踪了
Foster home in Pittsburgh reported you missing two weeks ago.
你要把我送回去吗
You're sending me back?
不
No.
他们不要你了
They don't want you.
-真惨  -你还笑
- Harsh. - You laugh,
但是你已经从六个城市的
but you've run from foster homes
寄养家庭离家出走了  巴特森先生
in six counties, Mr. Batson.
都是想要抚养你的好人家
From good people who want you,
为了寻找一个显然不想要你的人
all in pursuit of someone who arguably does not.
是时候和你把话说开了
It's time someone looked you in the eye and told it to you straight.
我不需要玩过家家的父母
I don't need parents to play make-believe with.
-我有妈妈  -没错
- I got a mom. - Yes.
你还真是个像样的侦探
You're some detective.
37个年龄在28到40之间姓巴特森的人
Seventy-three Batsons between the ages of 28 to 40,
你把每个都划掉了
and you've crossed out every one.
我还没有找到她  我知道的
She's still out there. I know it.
外面有一对夫妻  巴特森先生
There's a couple outside, Mr. Batson.
他们有一个儿童之家
They run a group home.
我能照顾好自己
I can take care of myself.
那也得等到你十八岁
When you're 18.
在那之前  我不会让你流浪街头
Until then, I won't have you living on the streets,
寻找一个从没找过你的人
looking for someone who never looked for you.
给这些人一个机会
Give these people a chance.
因为他们给了你机会
'Cause that's what they're giving you.
你没有别的选择了
You're out of options.
我就不废话了
I'm gonna skip the spiel.
只要知道我和罗莎  我们懂的
Just know that me and Rosa, we get it.
我们也是寄养家庭出身
We were foster kids back in the day.
在远古的黑暗时代
Back in the Dark Ages.
妹子  我的内心还很年轻
Girl, I'm young at heart.
我血脉贲张呢
I got my finger on the pulse.
这是在说他的血压  因为他老了
Yeah, that's a reference to his blood pressure because he's old.
比利  你对什么食物过敏吗
Billy, do you have any food allergies?
最好过敏  今天达拉做饭
Gonna wish you did. Darla's cooking.
怎么了
What?
我们知道这肯定让你很紧张
We know how overwhelming it can all be.
新家  新面孔
New house, new faces.
一下子要你接受
All up in your face.
以你自己的节奏慢慢来就好
Just take it at your own speed.
有人吗
Hello?
我们回来了
We're home.
你菜你活该
That's what happens when you suck!
欢迎派对可真棒
So much for the welcome party.
沙发上长出来的那个东西
Yeah, that thing growing out of the couch
是尤金
would be Eugene.
是他吗
Is that him?
天啊  比利
Oh, my gosh! Billy!
慢点  慢点
Slow down, slow down.
欢迎回家
Welcome home!
-这是达拉  -我是达拉
- And that's Darla. - I'm Darla.
-她很喜欢拥抱  -我发现了
- Big hugger. - I noticed.
去死  去死  去死
Die, die, die!
他不是那个意思  他在玩游戏
He doesn't mean that. It's a game.
天黑后不能喝汽水  还记得吗
No sodas after dark, remember?
什么时候天黑的
When did it get dark?
海报  我给你做了一张
The poster. I made you one.
快来看
Come look!
不
No!
欢迎回家
新来的哥哥
抱歉  肯定是佩德罗在锻炼
Sorry, Pedro must've been working out.
他想练得肌肉发达
His goal is to get swole.
只要一下  一下
Just one hit! Just one hit!
给你
Here.
没错  所以你们的数学系
Yes, exactly why your math department
-对我来说是独一无二的选择  -闭嘴  不
- is so uniquely suited for me. - Shut up! No!
我对尤金忍无可忍了
I can't even with Eugene right now.
抱歉  我是玛丽  你好  大学面试
I'm sorry. Mary, hi. College interview.
-我是比利  -我最期待的是什么
- I'm Billy. - What am I most excited about?
真是个好问题  你真是问到点子上了
What a great question. I was hoping you'd ask.
我最期待的是什么
What am I most excited about?
说你是寄养家庭的孩子  大学就吃这套
Mention you're a foster kid. Colleges eat that up.
我最期待的是校园生活
What I'm most excited about is the campus experience.
生长在寄养家庭  我坚信
As a foster child, I'm a big believer
在最不可能的地方
in finding family and friends
也能找到属于自己的朋友和家人
in the most unlikely of places.
我会非常想念她的
I'm gonna miss that girl so much.
加州理工  非常有声望的名校
It's Caltech. It's a very prestigious school.
而且远在加州
And also all the way in California.
但我们现在没必要聊这个
But we don't have to talk about that right now.
对我来说  这话题有些沉重
It's a tough subject for me.
你喜欢纯素食吗
Do you like vegan food?
因为我热爱动物
Because, see, I love animals.
不  我的素火鸡
No! The Tofurky!
不  这下我们只能吃真火鸡了
No, we may have to eat a real turkey!
-那是...  -没事的  来吧  我带你看看房间
- Is that... - It's okay. Come, I'll show you your room.
家里有点乱哄哄的  我知道  但也很有意思
It's a bit of a madhouse, I know, but it's fun.
老实受死吧
Time to dance on your grave!
小心脚下不平  佩德罗
Watch the bum step. Pedro...
亲爱的  跟比利打个招呼
Mi amor, say hi to Billy.
别往心里去  他对谁都这样
Don't take it personally. He's like that with everyone.
弗莱迪
Freddy.
这是比利·巴特森
This is Billy Batson.
你照顾下他  让他别那么拘束
Make sure you make him feel at home.
-好吗  -好
- Okay? - Yeah.
最好别说太奇怪的话
Maybe don't say anything too weird?
有一件奇怪的事  你知道吗
One weird thing is, did you know that
以前罗马人用自己的尿刷牙
Romans used to brush their teeth with their urine?
而且显然  效果很好
And apparently, it works.
还挺高的
It's a long way down.
相信我  这是经验之谈
Trust me, I speak from experience.
维克托把我推下去了
Victor pushed me.
他们看起来很友善  但是别上当
They seem nice, but don't buy it.
这里上演着现实版《权力的游戏》
It gets real Game of Thrones around here.
什么
What?
老兄  我瞎说的
Dude, I'm just messin' around.
其实是癌症晚期  我只剩三个月可活了
It's, um, terminal cancer. I only have three months.
还是开玩笑的  你看着我心里一定在想
Kidding, again! You look at me, and you're like,
"为什么要这么阴暗  你这个残废的寄养小孩"
"Why so dark? You're a disabled foster kid.
"没人比你更能搏同情了"  是吧
You've got it all." Right?
那是老蝙蝠镖
Yeah, that's the old Batarang.
这是复刻版  但你摸摸有多锋利
I mean, it's a replica, but feel how sharp.
星球日报
超人归来
我可以在你睡觉的时候用它杀了你
I could kill you in your sleep with that thing.
还是说你更喜欢超人
You more of a Supes guy?
哥谭自由出版社
超人
我也是  请看  我的宝物
Yeah, me, too. Behold, the holy grail.
一颗射中超人的九毫米口径子弹
One nine-millimeter round shot at Superman himself.
防伪证书
这是真货
It's legit.
我也说不好  大概值五六百吧  或者更多
Probably worth, I don't know, five, six hundred, maybe more.
你包里装了什么
What's in the bag?
没关系  保持界限是好事
Hey, it's all good. It's good to maintain boundaries.
不过你可以稍微说两句话的
You don't gotta talk so much, you know.
反正这地方特别好  你会喜欢上的
Anyway, this place is great. You're gonna love it.
蕾切尔·巴特森
车牌  C78AZ29
霍夫曼街21号
吃晚饭了
Dinner!
各就各位
All hands on deck.
感谢您赐予我们家人
Thank you for this family.
感谢您赐予我们今日
Thank you for this day.
感谢您赐予我们食物  即使不是菲力牛排
Thank you for this food, even if it's not steak filet.
学校很大  两千名学生  你或许会想
Big school. 2,000 students, you might think,
"这么多陌生人啊"
"Wow, so many strangers."
但把他们看作未来可能的朋友就不会这样想了
But not if you think of them as possible future friends.
就会变成  "这么多朋友啊"
Then it's, "Wow, so many friends."
校长叫做雪莉  她最好了
The principal, her name's Shirley. She's the best.
下一位
Next.
这是我们的安全扫描器
This is our security scanner.
和机场里的一样  非常安全
Like in an airport. It's totally safe.
我知道这是什么
I know what it is.
她总是这样吗
Does she always do this?
沉默使我感到不舒服
Silence makes me uncomfortable.
她鲜少感到不舒服
She's almost never uncomfortable.
祝你第一天过得愉快  哥哥
Have a good first day, big brother.
听着  你不用总是抱我
Look, you don't have to hug me all the time.
我们其实不是兄妹  所以...
We're not actually brother and sister, so...
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不是故意让她...
I didn't mean to make her...
说实话  我有些不知所措
I was overwhelmed, honestly.
他说我必须拥有至纯之心
He said I must be pure of heart.
他自称是一位巫师
He call himself a wizard.
他的打扮就像是《哈利·波特》里的巫师
He even dressed like a wizard from Harry Potter or some...
但你是说其他人也有过类似的经历吗
But you're saying that other people have experienced this?
可以这么说  你还记得他对你说了什么吗
In a sense, yes. Do you remember what he said to you?
他考验了我
He tested me.
那里有一些雕像
There were these statues.
他们的眼睛  好像在盯着我
Their eyes, it's like they were looking at me,
让我产生各种想法
making me think things.
可怕的想法
Horrible things.
这跟你看到的近似吗
And do these approximate what you saw?
是的  完全是我记忆中的样子
Yes, that's exactly how I remember it.
我不明白  你怎么知道...
I don't understand. How do you know...
在群体癔症中  复发性意象已被证实
Recurrent imagery has proven very common
是十分常见的
in cases of mass hysteria.
群体癔症
Mass hysteria?
我知道  这个名词有点夸张
I know. The term's a bit theatrical.
但就拿看到不明飞行物举例
But take UFO sightings, for example.
天空中的光  还有飞碟
Lights in the sky, flying saucers.
发生在互相不认识的人身上的独立事件...
Isolated incidents of people who do not know each other...
那些符号
The symbols.
问问她符号的事
Ask her about the symbols.
不好意思  关女士  但作为复发性意象的例子
Sorry, Ms. Kwan. But as an example of recurrent imagery,
在你所说的绑架发生前
maybe you'll recall seeing
你有看到这些符号吗
these symbols before the alleged abduction.
我不记得任何符号了
I don't remember any symbols, no.
我应该录下来了  有些东西...
I think I got it on video. There was something, um...
我记得闹钟上的数字
I remember the numbers on my alarm clock.
一直在变
They kept shifting.
录像
Video?
给我看录像
Show me the video.
关女士  这位是希瓦那博士
Ms. Kwan, this is Dr. Sivana.
稍等  我发给你
One moment, I can send it.
是谁  天啊
Hello? Oh, my God!
谁在那儿
Who's there?
是谁  怎么回事  发生什么了
Hello? What's going on? What's happening?
我要报警了
I'm going to call the police!
然后这束耀眼的光芒把我笼罩其中
Then this blinding light all around me
我感觉自己被拉进了什么
and I felt like I was getting pulled down into something.
感觉是一座建在山内部的寺庙
It felt like a temple carved inside a mountain.
他看起来和你想象中
He looked exactly what you'd expect from a guy
自称巫师的人一模一样
who calls himself a wizard.
以及你被带去是为了拯救世界
...and how you were brought there to save the world.
穿着一件斗篷  顶上没有天花板
Wearing a cape. And there's no ceiling.
我们再算一遍...
We ran the numbers again...
希瓦那博士
Dr. Sivana!
我欣赏你的热情  但你资助的是我的项目
I appreciate your enthusiasm, but you're funding my project.
我在询问的时候  不希望被打扰
And when I'm interviewing, I don't wanna be interrupted.
56起记录在案的绑架
Fifty-six recorded abductions.
-我一直没发现  -发现什么
- I never saw it. - Saw what?
博士  这些都是什么
Doctor, what is all this?
这么多年来
All these years...
我一直确信是我的序列不对
I was convinced I had the incorrect sequence.
或者可能是用错误的符号打开了门
Or perhaps the wrong symbols to open the door.
但在那个女人的闹钟上
But on that woman's alarm clock,
那七个符号
the seven symbols.
那个序列重复了七次
The sequence repeated itself seven times.
这就是差别所在
That's the difference.
你在开什么玩笑吗
Is this some sort of joke?
在你看来可能是玩笑
It may seem that way to you
因为实际上我们并不是在研究群体癔症
because we're not in actuality studying mass hysteria.
所有这些人看到的
What all these people have seen,
每个人看到的  都是绝对真实的
every single one of them, is absolutely real.
闹钟发生了故障
An alarm clock malfunctions
而你的第一反应是证明了巫师的存在吗
and your first thought is it's proof of a wizard?
拜托  希瓦那博士
Come on, Dr. Sivana.
你怎么能相信这是真的呢
You can't believe any of this is real.
但是我信
Why, yes.
我相信
Yes, I do.
我为这一刻已经等待了太久
I've been waiting for this moment for so long...
如今我们又见面了
and now here we are.
你不记得我了  对吗
You don't remember me, do you?
我记得你
I remember you.
那时的小男孩
You were a boy.
现在你居然敢擅闯我的王国
And now you dare intrude in my kingdom.
你知道作为孩子  被告知永远不够优秀
Do you know what it's like for a child to be told
是什么感受吗
you'll never be good enough?
你不知道
No, you don't.
多年前你对我说的话
What you said to me all those years ago
让我意识到自己到底是什么样的人
made me realize who I really was.
你知道吗
And you know something?
我没有至纯之心
I am not pure of heart.
巫师已经虚弱到无法阻止我们了
The wizard is too weak to stop us.
不
No!
你没能找到你的继承者
You never found your champion.
但我们找到了我们的
But we found ours.
你是真正的继承者
You are the true champion.
他们在利用你
They're using you.
你对他们来说不过是逃走的工具
You're nothing to them but a means of escape.
通过你  他们会毒害所接触到的一切
Through you, they'll spread their poison to everything they touch!
让人类自相残杀
Make mankind turn on each other!
你想要至纯的灵魂  老头
You seek a pure soul, old man,
但没人配得上
but no one's worthy.
福西特学校
飞行还是隐形
Flight or invisibility?
如果你能拥有超能力的话
If you could have one superpower,
飞行还是隐形  你会选哪个
flight or invisibility, what would you pick?
每个人都选飞行  你知道为什么吗
I mean, everybody chooses flight. You know why?
为了可以飞着逃离这个对话吗
So they can fly away from this conversation?
不  因为英雄都会飞
No, no. 'Cause heroes fly.
谁不想让别人认为自己是英雄呢  对吧
And who doesn't want people to think they're a hero, right?
但是隐形  绝对不行
But invisibility, no way I mean.
那是变态
That's pervy.
到处偷窥那些察觉不到你的人
Spying around on people who don't even know you're there.
鬼鬼祟祟  完全是反派的能力  对吧
Sneaking around everywhere. It's a total villain power, right?
垃圾
然后人们做了个研究  这是真事
Then they did this study, and this is a real thing.
他们问了同样的问题
They asked people the same question.
你想要什么超能力
You know, what power do you want?
但这次  回答是匿名的
But this time, they made it so the answers were anonymous.
一旦知道是保密的
And most people, since they knew
大多数人都选了隐形
that it was secret, said invisibility.
我认为那是因为大多数人
And I think that's 'cause most people
内心深处都不认为自己是英雄
don't feel like heroes on the inside, deep down.
你要离家出走了
You're gonna run away.
男厕
我是说  你偷了我的超人子弹
I mean, you stole my Superman bullet.
老兄  我懂  我真的懂
Dude, I get it. I get it.
你被坑了太多次
You've been screwed over way too many times.
你谁也不相信
You don't trust anyone.
隐形也是这样的
That's the thing about invisibility.
最终只剩你一个人
You end up all by yourself.
我没偷你的破子弹
I didn't steal your dumb bullet.
今天怎么样
How was it today?
这么好是吗
That good, huh?
天啊  弗莱迪
Oh, my God! Freddy.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
-你没事吧  -没事
- You okay? - Yes. Yes.
搞什么
What the hell?
你们两个什么毛病
What is wrong with you two?
这刮痕肯定除不掉了
No way that's gonna buff out.
你要怎么赔偿  弗里曼
You gonna pay for that, Freeman?
赔偿你差点撞到我搞出的坑吗
For the dent you made almost hitting me?
当然可以
Yeah, sure.
你们收这个吗
You guys take these?
布莱特  住手
Brett, stop!
别碰我哥哥
Don't touch my brother!
怎么  你还得靠冒牌家人替你出头吗
What, do you need your fake family to stand up for you?
-捍卫自己  弗里曼  -是啊
- Stand up for yourself, Freeman. - Yeah, huh?
弗里曼  给你  还手啊
Freeman, here, stand up.
捍卫自己
Stand up for yourself.
你打算怎么办  哭着回家找妈妈吗
What are you gonna do, go home and cry to Mommy?
对了  你没有妈妈
Oh, yeah. You don't have a mommy.
真不好意思
Man, sorry about that.
偷袭不太好  不过你们也不会光明正大
That wasn't fair, but then again you don't fight fair, so...
退后  混蛋们  我知道怎么用这玩意儿
Back off, assbags. I know how to use these things.
-他跑了  -你去哪儿
- He's getting away! - Where you going?
弗莱迪  你没事吧
Freddy, are you okay?
我们从后面包抄
Let's go through the back.
你跑不掉的
Nowhere to run!
快  抓住他  让开
Go, go, go! Grab him! Move!
市场-法兰克福线
前往法兰克福和第六十九街
别挡道  让开  女人
Get out the way. Move, woman!
不不不
No, no, no.
你死定了  小鬼
You're dead, kid.
你以为自己很搞笑
Yeah, you think you're funny.
我们知道你在哪上学  伙计
We know where you go to school, buddy!
下一站  第三十街
Next stop, 30th Street Station.
可换乘市域轨道交通线路
Change for the regional rail lines.
下一站  第三十街
有人吗
Hello?
怎么回事
What's going on?
救命
Help!
好吧
Okay.
天哪
Holy moly.
市场-法兰克福线
有人吗
Hello?
怎么回事
What the hell?
这是谁干的
Who's doing this?
你好
Hi.
我本来要在第三十街下车
I was supposed to get off at 30th.
比利·巴特森
Billy Batson.
你怎么知道我的名字
How'd you know my name?
我是巫师议会的最后一位成员
I am the last of the Council of Wizards.
永恒之石的守护者
Keeper of the Rock of Eternity.
你就是...
You're...
那个人
that guy.
听着  我身上一分钱都没有
Hey, listen, I don't have any money.
别跟我耍小聪明  小子
Do not patronize me, boy.
你现在身处一切魔法之源
You are standing in the source of all magic.
永恒之石  七巫师的宝座
The Rock of Eternity. Seven thrones of seven wizards.
但很久以前  我们选择了一位继承者
But long ago, we chose a champion
却未经深思熟虑
and we chose recklessly.
他将力量用于复仇
He used his power for revenge,
将七宗罪引入人世
releasing the Seven Deadly Sins into your world.
数百万生灵涂炭
Millions of lives were lost.
文明被从世间完全抹去
Entire civilizations erased from existence.
于是我发誓再也不传授我的魔法
That is why I vowed never to pass on my magic
除非找到一个真正善良的人
until I find one truly good person.
精神强韧
Strong in spirit,
内心纯洁
pure in heart.
听着  伙计  也许这是魔法
Look, man, maybe this is magic
我不知道  但是
and, I don't know, but
你要找的善良纯洁的人
the people you're looking for, good, pure people,
我不属于那一类
I'm not one of them.
我怀疑根本没有那样的人
I don't know if anyone is, really.
比利·巴特森
You, Billy Batson,
你是我唯一的希望
are all I have.
也是这个世界唯一的希望
All the world has.
把手放在我的权杖上
Lay your hands on my staff.
变态
Gross.
并说出我的名字  我才能把力量传给你
And say my name so my powers may flow through you.
我向你敞开心扉  比利·巴特森
I open my heart to you, Billy Batson.
这意味着  我选择你作为继承者
And in so doing, choose you as champion.
谢了
Thanks.
先生  你人真好  但我真的得走了
Real sweet of you, mister, but I really gotta get going.
我的兄弟姐妹惨遭七宗罪杀害
My brothers and sisters were slain by the Sins.
他们的宝座空空如也
Their thrones lie empty.
我的魔法必须传承下去
My magic must be passed on.
现在  说出我的名字
Now, speak my name!
我不知道你的名字  先生  我们刚见面
I don't know your name, sir. We just met.
我的名字是...
My name is...
沙赞
Shazam.
等等  真的吗
Wait, for real?
-快说  -好
- Say it! - Okay!
天哪
Jeez.
直接说吗  就...
So just say it? Like...
沙赞
Shazam?
对
Yes!
记住我的名字  它将赐予你我的全部力量
Carry my name, and with it, you carry all my powers.
所罗门的智慧  海格力斯的力量
The wisdom of Solomon, the strength of Hercules,
所罗门是古代犹太国王  《旧约·列王纪》称其有超人的智慧
海格力斯是希腊神话中的大力神
阿特拉斯的耐力  宙斯的力量
the stamina of Atlas, the power of Zeus,
阿特拉斯是希腊神话中的擎天巨神
宙斯是希腊神话中的众神之王
阿喀琉斯的勇气  墨丘利的速度
the courage of Achilles, and the speed of Mercury.
阿喀琉斯是荷马史诗《伊利亚特》中参加特洛伊战争的半神英雄
墨丘利是罗马神话中众神的使者
我这是怎么了  为什么我...
What happened to me? Why am...
你对我做了什么  我的声音怎么变成这样了
What did you do to me? What did you do to my voice?
你被激发出了全部的潜能  比利·巴特森
You have been transformed to your full potential, Billy Batson.
用你的心  释放你最强大的力量
With your heart, unlock your greatest power.
我们兄弟姐妹的宝座正在等待
The thrones of our brothers and sisters await.
让我离开这里
Get me outta here!
酷毙了
Dope!
兄弟  我为你今天的穿着鼓掌
My brother, I applaud your choices today.
金鞋子  金腰带  白披风
Gold shoes, gold belt, white cape.
这搭配烂透了  但你穿着真他妈帅
It shouldn't work, but hot damn, it does!
宝贝
Babe!
是的  警官
Yes, Officer.
我知道他以前离家出走过
I'm aware he's run away in the past.
离家出走了23次
Twenty-three times?
这家伙完全没用过社交媒体
Guy's got no social media presence. At all.
他就是个幽灵
The guy is a ghost.
不及格
各位  我很乐意去找比利
You know, guys, I'm happy to look for Billy.
非常乐意
More than happy.
但我得把碗洗了
But no, you gotta wash the dishes.
这件事更重要
That's what's more important.
"你能怎么办  弗莱迪  追着他跑吗"
"What are you gonna do, Freddy, run after him?"
真搞笑
Very funny.
别尖叫
不  我说了  别尖叫
No, I said, don't scream.
-维克托  维克托  -别叫了
- Victor? Victor! - No, no!
-维克托  -是我  我是比利
- Victor! - It's me. It's Billy.
我是比利
It's Billy!
你问我选飞行还是隐形  当时我觉得很蠢
You asked me flight or invisibility. I thought that was stupid,
但现在我变成了这样  我需要你的帮助
but now I look like this and I need your help.
熄灯之后来外面找我
Meet me back here after lights-out?
怎么了  孩子  你没事吧
'Sup, bud? You all right?
没事  我只是...
Yeah. Yeah. I'm just...
比利走了  我很难过
I'm really sad because Billy's gone.
也许是我的错  也许是因为我
And, you know, maybe it's my fault. Maybe I did it.
也许是因为我打呼噜
You know, maybe I snore.
孩子  不是你的错  知道吗
Not your fault, son, all right?
我们会找到他的  好吗
We'll find him, 'kay?
你打呼噜没那么响
You don't snore that bad.
但你身上有点臭
But you kinda smell.
谢天谢地
Thank God!
别过来
Stop right there.
我怎么知道你不是
How do I know you're not a supervillain
利用心灵感应能力
using telepathic abilities
让我认为你是比利的超级反派
to make me believe that you're Billy?
-什么  -我只需要按下呼叫键
- What? - All I have to do is press "dial" on this thing.
别  我有证据  我有证据  在这里
No! No, I have proof. I have proof. Here.
听着  我撒谎了  我拿了你的子弹
Look, I lied, okay? I took your bullet.
-不  不不不  -不
- Oh, no! No, no, no. - No!
大人的手笨死了
Stupid adult hands.
但你看到了
But you saw it.
你看到了吧
You saw it, right?
弗莱迪  我发誓是我  好吗
Look, Freddy, I swear. It's me, okay?
我知道我们不算是好朋友
Look, I know we're not really close friends or anything,
但你是我认识的人里面
but you're the only person that I know
唯一一个了解披风斗士那一套的人
that knows anything about this caped crusader stuff.
蝙蝠侠的另一个称呼
-那是蝙蝠侠  -什么
- That's Batman. - What?
当我没说
Forget it.
能让我...
Can I...
当然
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
天哪
Oh, my God!
太疯狂了  对吧
It's crazy, right?
你的超能力是什么
What are your superpowers?
超能力
Superpowers?
老兄  我都不知道穿着这玩意怎么撒尿
Dude, I don't even know how to pee in this thing.
好吧  那你会飞吗
Okay. Can you fly?
好了  开始吧
Okay! Let's do this.
怎么做来着
How do we do this?
像超人那样就行了
Just, um, like, Superman it.
天哪  很明显你得跳起来
Oh, my God. Obviously, you have to jump.
来吧
Come on.
哪里明显了
How is any of this obvious?
好吧
Okay.
试着相信自己会飞  好吗
Try, uh, to believe that you can fly. Okay?
我读了一篇深入解析
I read this deep dive
业内认可的超能力研究的文章
into peer-reviewed studies about superpowers
里面说六成超能力的关键在于信念
and in six out of ten, belief is the key.
信念  信念  信念  好吧
Belief. Belief. Belief. Okay. Okay.
我相信我会飞
I believe I can fly.
我相信我...
I believe I...
我相信我会飞
I believe I can fly.
我相信我...
I believe I...
你相信了吗
Did you believe?
相信了
Yeah.
你想试试隐形吗
You wanna try invisibility?
我怎么才能...
How do I do...
算了  好吧
Forget it. You know, okay.
好吧  好吧  好吧
Okay, okay, okay.
天哪  成功了
Oh, my God! It worked!
你去哪儿了
Where'd you go?
我就在这里  你看不到我吗
I'm right here. You can't see me?
哪里
Where?
我隐形了
I'm invisible!
我就在这里  就在这里
I'm right here. Over here.
我隐形了  我隐形了
I'm invisible! I'm invisible!
行头不错  蠢货
Nice outfit, dipshit.
我刚刚可能是在同时测试
I might've been testing invisibility
隐形能力和超级智力
and super-intelligence at the same time.
弗里曼  我要过去打你了
Freeman, I'm gonna come over there and beat you.
天哪  你胸口的闪电标记
Oh, my God! The lightning emblem!
一直摆在我们眼前
It was staring us right in the face the whole time.
真的
Literally!
好了
Okay, okay.
显然  我们得给你
Clearly, we gotta give you
-取一个和闪电有关的超级英雄名字  -嗯
- a lightning-themed superhero name. - Yeah.
对了
Oh, right.
那边的  让...
Hey, you! Back...
开
off.
超高速  确认
Hyper-speed, check.
抱歉  很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
我还以为是你在喊
I thought you were the one who was screaming.
我用辣椒喷雾喷了他
I doused him with pepper spray.
明智之举
Smart move.
抢劫犯先生  把老太太的包还给她
Yeah, hey, Mr. Mugger Guy. Give the old lady her purse back.
我跟你同龄
I'm your age.
而且他没机会
And he didn't get a chance
抢走我的包  因为我没让他得逞
to take it 'cause I didn't let him take it.
很好  很好  你真的很擅长这个
Good. Yeah, good. You're really on top of this stuff.
这件事给你的教训是  老太太...
And that should teach you that old ladies...
像你这样平常年纪的女士
Regular-aged ladies like yourself
不需要你的保护  明白吗
don't need your protecting, right?
清醒点吧  老兄
So get woke, bro.
不好意思  你是谁
I'm sorry, who are you?
他叫雷鸣霹雳
His name is Thundercrack,
他是人民的英雄
hero to the people
集闪电的力量和速度于一体
with all the power and speed of lightning all in one.
老兄  这名字听起来像是在说屁股
Dude, that sounds like a butt thing.
buttcrack  屁股缝
费城先生
Mister Philadelphia.
像卖奶油干酪的  老兄
That's a cream cheese thing, dude!
Philadelphia是知名奶油干酪品牌
力量小子  因为他拥有全部的力量
Power Boy. 'Cause he's got all the powers.
因为有时候辣椒喷雾没法抵御邪恶
'Cause sometimes pepper spray can't protect against evil.
力量小子  你认识这个小孩吗
Power Boy, do you know this child?
稍微认识一丢丢  我们不太熟...
Like a teeny little bit. I don't really know...
嗯  他就像我的迷你经纪人
Yeah. He's like a little miniature manager.
我是他的经纪人
I'm his manager.
但也不能叫力量小子  好吗
But Power Boy's not gonna work, either, okay?
神力小子是DC漫画旗下真实存在的超级英雄
还是想想别的名字吧
So work on something else.
伙计  怎么...
Bud, what could...
操控电力  超高速  超级力量
Electricity manipulation, hyper-speed, super-strength.
老兄  你简直无所不能
Dude, you're stacked!
你几乎和超人一样酷了  几乎
You're almost as cool as Superman. Almost.
我没见过你  我不知道刚刚发生了什么
I didn't see you. I don't know what just happened here.
我不想知道  别伤害我
I don't wanna know. Just don't hurt me.
我这么做不是为了钱
I'm not doing it for the money.
谢谢你慷慨的捐赠
Thank you for your kind donation.
不不不  但如果以后你需要帮助
No, no, no, but if you ever need any more help
找我这个不会飞的超级英雄就行
just look for the superhero that still can't fly.
别想飞的事了  我们刚赚了73块
Forget flying, man. We just made 73 bucks!
73块
Seventy-three bucks?
真给力
Come on!
等一下
Wait a minute.
我有个主意
I just got an idea.
我想买一些这里最好的啤酒
I'd like to purchase some of your finest beer, please.
我觉得不妥  我们连假身份证都没有
I don't know about this. I mean, we don't have a fake ID even.
弗莱迪  弗莱迪  放松点行吗
Freddy, Freddy, would you relax?
看看我  我就是假身份证
Look at me. I am the fake ID.
把收银机里的钱都拿出来
Everything from the register!
快点  快
Go, go! Now!
快点  没时间了  快点
Come on! We don't have any time. Let's go. Move!
一分钱也别落下  快点
We want it all! Hurry.
你的机会来了
This is your chance.
好的
Okay.
快点  把钱拿出来
Come on, come on, come on! Let's do this!
没错  就是这样
That's it. That's it.
先生们
Gentlemen,
不如把枪放下  像真男人一样处理这件事
why use guns when we can handle this like real men?
比利  当心
Billy, look out!
防弹  你有防弹能力
Bullet immunity. You have bullet immunity!
我是防弹的
I'm bulletproof.
今天是12月8日
Today is December 8th,
这是证明真实性的视频
and this is video proof of authenticity.
再打他一枪
Shoot him again.
对对对  拿着  你们俩一起开枪
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Here, here. Go. Both of you!
来吧  随便打
Come on. Go to town.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait.
我们还是不知道是衣服防弹
We still don't know if the suit is bulletproof,
还是你防弹
or if you are.
开枪打他的脸
Shoot him in the face.
开枪打我的脸  打我的脸
Shoot me in the face. In the face?
有点痒
It kinda tickles.
你们完了
You're dead.
-抱歉打碎了窗户  -祝你今晚愉快
- Sorry about your window. - Have a good night!
但我们让你免遭抢劫  不客气
But you're welcome for not getting robbed!
快走  快离开这里
Come on! Let's get outta here.
-敬打击坏蛋  -好
- To fighting bad guys. - Yeah.
味道像呕吐物
That tastes like actual vomit.
你知道吗  如果吃太多哈瓦那肉干
Do you know habanero jerky, if you eat enough of it,
你的胃会被烧出一个洞
it can burn a hole in your stomach?
值了
Worth it.
嗯  但你应该不会
Yeah. Probably not you, though.
你的胃应该有超能力
You've probably got stomach superpowers.
应该吧
Probably.
你好  我是超级英雄
What's up? I'm a superhero.
没错  他的名字是
Yeah, his name is, uh,
火花手指队长
Captain Sparklefingers.
不  才不是  那不是我的名字
No, it's not. No, it's not! That's not my name.
我们该一起去玩  我们年龄相仿
We should hang out. We're, like, the same age.
好吧  我溜了
Okay. I'm out.
等等我
Wait up!
这景色太美了
I mean, it's a pretty sick view.
我明白洛奇为了来这为什么训练得那么努力了
I totally get why Rocky was training so hard to get up here.
电影《洛奇》中为和世界冠军对阵而刻苦训练的拳手
我喜欢这样的你  太酷了
You know, I like you like this. This is so cool.
无意冒犯
I mean, no offense,
但起初你就像是
but, like, at first you were kinda like
和达拉截然相反的人
the opposite of how Darla is.
是混蛋吗
A dick?
这是你说的  不是我
Your words. Not mine.
但确实如此
But yeah.
好了  我感觉现在所有的犯罪分子
All right, well, I feel like every criminal
不是在嗑药就是睡着了
is either on drugs or asleep by now.
想回家吗
Wanna head home?
这幅样子回家吗
Looking like this?
是啊
Well, yeah,
通常来说  我们应该有个据点
I mean, usually, we'd have a lair to go back to,
但那需要从长计议
but that's long-term.
现在  我们有一张双层床
Right now, we have a bunk bed.
一想到他在外孤身一人我就感到不安
Just scares me thinking of him out there all alone.
他经常这么做  罗莎
This is what he does, Rosa.
区别在于  等他们找到他
Difference is, when they find him,
我们会是第一家接纳他的人
we'll be the first to take him back.
敞开胸怀接纳他
With open arms.
甚至还不到两天  还不到两天
Didn't even make it two days. Not even two days.
亲爱的  我们以前也离家出走过
Baby, we did our fair share of running off back when.
至少我离家出走过
At least I did.
-嗯  -连玛丽也离家出走过
- Yeah. - Even Mary did it.
而且是两次
Twice.
她第二次离家出走的时候
That second time she ran off,
你跟我说了一句我永远忘不了的话
you said something to me I'll never forget.
你说
You said,
"你把它称之为家  它才是真的家"
"It's not a home until you call it a home.
"家是你自己选择的"
It's something you choose."
我们能做的只有给他一个充满爱的环境
All we can do is give him a place full of love.
他是否把这里称之为家  由他自己决定
Whether he chooses to call it a home, that's up to him.
嗯
Yeah.
来帮我一起装扮这棵树吗
You gonna help me with this tree?
这棵树太老土了
This tree's so sad.
有人吗
Hello?
我刚刚找不到厕所
Got lost finding the bathroom.
好吧  弗莱迪  亲爱的  晚安
Okay, Freddy, sweetie. Good night.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night. - Night.
弗莱迪  那是谁
Freddy, who is that?
是比利  他很累了  而且他得了喉炎
It's Billy. He's just really tired and he has laryngitis.
什么  喉炎
What? Laryngitis!
开玩笑的  开玩笑的
I'm just kidding! I'm just kidding.
他真的很累了  他想睡觉觉了
He's really, really tired, and he wants to go to beddy-bye.
-睡觉觉  谁会说睡觉觉  -快躲起来
- Beddy-bye? Who says beddy-bye? - Just hide, hide.
比利  你回来了  让我们看看你
Billy, you're back. Let us see you.
我们一直很担心你
We've been so worried about you.
我跟你说了这是个坏主意
I told you this was a bad idea!
弗莱迪
Freddy?
弗莱迪  楼梯怎么了
Freddy, what happened to the stairs?
像要绑架她一样捂住她的嘴
Covering her mouth like you're gonna kidnap her
反而会让她更害怕  好吗
is not gonna make her less scared, okay?
达拉  是我  比利  我知道看起来不像
Darla, it's me. It's Billy. I know I don't look like me.
一个巫师把我变成了这样
A wizard made me look like this.
还是先别提"巫师"这回事
Maybe don't start with "wizard."
这会让她更困惑
It's just gonna make her more confused.
有个老头把我带到一座神庙
Some old guy brought me to a temple
然后逼我说"沙赞"
and he made me say, "Shazam."
罗莎
Rosa!
口头触发的变身能力
Verbally triggered body-manipulation properties!
你可以说"沙赞"来切换形态
You can switch by saying, "Shazam."
亲爱的  是你弄的吗  你没事吧
Baby, was that you? Are you okay?
我刚刚在拧一个灯泡
I was screwing in a bulb.
听我说  达拉
Listen to me, Darla.
你不能跟任何人说这件事  好吗
You cannot tell anybody about this, all right?
但这是比利  他是个英雄
But it's Billy. He's a hero.
嗯  但如果被超级反派发现他是英雄
Yeah, but if a supervillain finds out that he's a hero,
会威胁到我们的安全  知道吗
that endangers us, okay?
英雄的家人是坏蛋的绝佳目标
A hero's loved ones are the perfect bad guy target.
她擅长保守秘密吗
I mean, is she even good at keeping secrets?
-一般般吧  -不擅长
- Moderate. - No.
天哪
Oh, God.
好吧  听着  小达
Okay, listen, D,
你不能跟任何人提起这件事  好吗  拜托
you cannot tell a single soul about this, all right? Please?
为什么  如果是我们信任的人呢
Why? What if it's people we trust?
因为好妹妹会保守秘密
Because good sisters don't tell secrets.
-我是好妹妹  -没错  你是
- I'm a good sister. - Yeah, you are.
你知道怎么变成更好的妹妹吗
You know what'd make you an even better sister?
就是帮我们把门把手修好  好吗
Is if you fixed the doorknob for us, okay?
嗯
Yeah.
-晚安  -晚安  再见
- Sweet dreams. - Sweet dreams. Bye.
-明早见  -晚安
- See you in the morning. - Good night.
希瓦那工业
你好  先生  有什么事吗
Hello, sir. How may I help you?
你好  先生
Hi. Sir?
先生  你不能进去  不好意思
Sir, you can't go in there. Excuse me!
你不能进去
You cannot go in there!
抱歉我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
萨德  董事会成员才能参加会议
Thad, this is for board members only.
我知道  父亲
I'm aware of that, Father.
好了  那晚在车里
Now, that night in the car.
我向你发誓我看见了什么  但你从来不相信我
I swore to you I saw something, but you never believed me.
责备我容易多了  不是吗
So much easier to blame me, wasn't it?
你还说如果我那晚没有尖叫
And say that if I hadn't screamed that night,
你就不会失去自己的双腿
you'd still have your legs.
现在我有证据了
Well, now I have proof.
够了  萨德
That's enough, Thad.
是吗  亲爱的希德
Dear Sid, you think?
在那起事故之前  你就看不起我
You know, even before the accident, you belittled me.
别逼我把你扔出去  萨德
Don't make me throw you outta here, Thad.
你没必要大吵大闹
You don't need to make a scene.
哥哥
Brother,
这仅仅是个开始
the scene has only just begun.
问问它你能不能把我扔出去
Ask that if you can throw me out.
什么
What?
问问这个球  你是否有种把我扔出去
Ask the ball if you're man enough to throw me out of this room.
我来告诉你吧
Let me spoil it for you.
前景不理想
Outlook not so good.
我在圣诞节来到这里  给予你...
I've come here during the season of giving to give you...
你应得的下场
what you deserve.
快跑
Run!
天啊  不
Oh, my God! No!
不  不
No! No!
救命
Help!
来人啊
Somebody!
救救我
Help me!
你不能总是找别人哭诉
You can't go crying to other people all the time.
哪宗罪最适合你呢  父亲
What sin best befits you, Father?
我什么都给你
I'll give you anything.
钱
Money.
公司  你想要公司吗
The company. You want the company?
我知道了
There it is.
贪婪
Greed.
你难道真的认为
Do you honestly think
你积累的这些物质财富
all this material you've accumulated
等于真正的权力吗
amounts to actual power?
这才是权力
This is power.
远胜你所拥有过的
More than you ever had.
远胜任何人
More than anyone has.
有一个更强大的人
There is one more powerful.
巫师找到自己的继承者了
The wizard found his champion.
在继承者发掘真正的潜能之前  杀了他
Kill the champion before he learns his true potential,
否则他会打败你
or he will defeat you.
告诉我他在哪里
Show me where to find him.
贪婪
Greed,
他是你的了
you can have him.
不
No.
不  不  不
No. Oh, no!
No! No! No!
家庭不仅仅是一个词
Family is more than just a word.
希瓦那工业专注于家庭
At Sivana Industries, our focus is family.
伯克
Burke.
车呢
Where's the truck?
我能听见
I can hear it.
天哪
Oh, my God!
我的车
My truck!
-我的车  -开什么玩笑
- My truck! - Are you kidding?
伙计们
You know, guys,
我觉得这下修不好了
I don't think that's gonna buff out.
让瘸腿的小孩干脏活  真有你的
Making the crippled kid do the dirty work. Wow!
我更适合望风  我能装无辜
I'm a better lookout. I can play innocent.
我就不能吗
And I can't?
你的脸给人一种很强烈的
Your face gives off a very strong vibe
要干坏事的感觉
of someone who's hatching schemes.
-我的脸  这张脸吗  -没错
- My face? This face? - Yeah. Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
你们有通行证吗
You boys got a hall pass?
我们吗  当然有
Us? Yeah. Always.
你
You!
你好像在打什么鬼主意
You look like you're up to something.
我  打鬼主意
Me? Up to something?
不  我从来没打过鬼主意
No. Never am I up to something.
爸爸要来接我们  他有事耽误了...
Our dad's picking us up. He got held up at the...
营业处有事
The business office.
营业处是吗
The business office, huh?
好吧  孩子
Sure, kid.
听着  家长或监护人
Look, parents or guardians
必须本人亲自到场来接学生
must appear physically to check out students.
明白
Gotcha.
好吧  你听到了吗  爸
Okay, well, you hear that, Dad?
沙赞
Shazam!
你好啊  儿子
Well, hey there, son,
你好啊  我另外一个跟刚刚在
and hey there, other son that I also have
走廊里碰见的儿子有血缘关系的儿子
that's related to that son I just passed in the hallway.
很抱歉我迟到了  我在营业处有事耽搁了
I'm so sorry I'm late. I got held up at the business office,
忙工作
doing all the work stuff.
这就是那个所有孩子都很崇拜的保安吧
This is the security guard all the kids admire so much.
其实是另一个  这个保安很差劲
Actually, that's the other one. This one sucks.
一点也不好笑
That's not funny.
我会好好和他说说的  抱歉
I'm gonna talk to him about that. I apologize.
总之  现在我亲自到场
Anyway, this is me appearing physically
领我的儿子们放学
to check my sons out of school.
非常感谢你保证孩子们的安全  白痴警探
So, thank you so much for keeping 'em safe, Detective Moron.
我叫莫兰
It's Moran.
-准备好了吗  -代数
- You ready? - Algebra!
科学
Science!
英文
English!
保健
Health!
警告
接下来是超级英雄的特技表演
在其经纪人监管之下
不要像白痴一样在家里尝试
超级力量  测试一
飞行  测试二
你没事吧
Are you okay?
激光眼  测试一
超高速 √
超级力量 √
飞行
逆转时间
心灵感应
吞噬物质
激光眼
瞬间移动  测试一
偷偷测试防火  测试一
对不起
I'm sorry!
防火
红色旋风超级力量测试
英雄经纪人
力量小子在抢劫案中挡下子弹
美国电长瞬间移动测试
正在上传
美国电长瞬间移动测试  第三回
上传完毕
超级力量测试十三
播放次数
美国电长防火测试
订阅人数
上传完毕
比火车头还要强大
More powerful than a locomotive.
火车头  你是矿工老头吗
Locomotive. What are you? An old prospector?
能一跃跳上摩天大楼
Can leap tall buildings in a single bound.
飞身一跃
Single bound.
对不起  真对不起
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry!
对不起  大家好
I'm sorry, people. Hi.
你的手机充满了
Your phone's charged.
做完拉风的事情后  你真的需要
You really need like a mic drop catchphrase
一句帅气的口头禅
after you do some cool shit.
我一直在想这个
I've been thinking about that.
这个怎么样
What about this?
"这就是不能乱玩电的原因"
"That's why you don't mess with electricity."
显然你也没有想口头禅的超能力
Catchphrases obviously aren't one of your superpowers.
你的手机充满了
And your phone's charged.
-你觉得你能想出更好的吗  -搞什么
- Well, you think you can do better? - What the hell?
电光闪耀吧
Let there be light.
胡椒博士汽水
就是这样  宝贝  多来点
Yeah, yeah, baby. Yeah, baby, okay.
我怎么脱...算了
How do I... Never mind.
沙赞
Shazam!
脱衣舞俱乐部
臀陷酒吧
免费辣鸡翅
脱衣舞俱乐部
臀陷酒吧
你看到什么了  看到什么了  有大胸吗
What'd you see? What'd you see? Were there boobies?
看到乳头了吗  你为什么不说话
You see nipples? Why aren't you talking?
我们需要更多的钱
We're gonna need more money.
为什么  你只待了五分钟
Why? You were in there for, like, five minutes.
老兄  她们超有说服力的
Dude, they were very convincing!
快拿  快拿
Get it, get it!
快走  快走
Go, go, go!
不
No!
住手  不
Stop! No!
-我都没在看  -住手
- I'm not even looking! - Stop!
住手
Stop.
-我都没在看  -住手
- I'm not even looking! - Stop!
-为什么  -结束了
- Why? - Oh, and done!
干掉他了
Finished him.
费城房地产
据点
A lair.
对
Yes.
而且显然
And obviously,
我们必须要匿名购买
we're gonna have to be making this purchase anonymously.
显然
Obviously.
如果你在悬崖上有物业
And, um, if you have a location on a cliff.
比如城堡那种
Like a castle-esque type thing.
-可以俯瞰水面  -俯瞰水面
- Overlooking some water. - Overlooking some water,
俯瞰大海  波涛汹涌那种
seas, below it. Rough, you know...
比如说瀑布
Like a waterfall,
-这样就能开车进入瀑布  -瀑布  没错
- so you can drive into... - Waterfall, yeah. If you... Yeah.
听着  你是最大电压  是吗
Look, Maximum Voltage, is it?
你可以叫我麦克斯
You can call me Max.
听着  麦克斯  不如这样吧
Look, Max, why don't you just start with
先说说你想要几间卧室
how many bedrooms you're looking for?
-一间  -七间
- One! - Seven.
- One? - Seven?
怎么  现在是我开寄养家庭了吗
What, am I running a foster home now?
你看过那个把足球扔进太空的视频吗
Have you seen the one where he throws the football into space?
酷毙了
So dope.
你们一定想知道是谁拍的  对吧
You guys gotta wonder who's filming those, right?
拍摄本身就很有勇气
I mean, that's bravery in and of itself.
真的吗
I mean, is it, though?
是啊  其实我还想说  远不只是勇气呢
Yeah. I'd actually argue maybe even more brave.
只是举着相机
Holding a camera?
直面危险
Staring in the face of danger.
就像个奇怪的粉丝
Like some weirdo fanboy.
弗里曼
Freeman.
如果我是你  我就不会这么做
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
怎么  你的闺蜜这次要用轮椅来打我们吗
What, is your bestie gonna hit us with a wheelchair this time?
不  也许不是他  但我有另一个好朋友
No, maybe not him, but I have another best friend
他也许会抓住你们  把你们消灭
who might hunt you down and destroy both of you.
好了  弗莱迪
Okay, Freddy.
你们也许听说过他  人力风暴
You may have heard of him. The Human Power Storm.
频环  活力先生
Frequency Flinger. Sir Zaps-A-Lot.
嗯  他有很多名字
Yeah. He's a man of many names.
你认识红色旋风
You know the Red Cyclone?
就你吗  你认识才怪
You? My ass you do.
我们比你想象的要亲近得多
We're a lot closer than you think.
也许此时此刻就很近
Maybe even at this very moment.
证明
Prove it.
明天我会证明的  明天他会来吃午餐
I will, tomorrow. Tomorrow he's gonna come to lunch.
对吧  比利
Right, right, Billy?
是吗  到时候
Oh, yeah, and then
超人还会给我们端甜点  是吧
Superman's gonna be bringing us dessert, right?
明天午餐时间  你们就知道了
Tomorrow at lunch. You'll see.
如果他不来  我们就痛扁你
And when he doesn't show, then we'll kick your ass.
等等  我的身份是保密的
So, wait, my identity's a secret
这样我认识的人才不会受伤
so no one I know can get hurt.
除非那能让你看起来很酷  那就没问题
Except when it makes you look cool, then it's all good.
比利  他们又不是超级反派
Billy, it's not like they're supervillains.
他们只是超级贱人而已
They're just super douchebags.
所以你要破坏自己的规矩吗
So, you're breaking your own rule?
懂了
Got it.
这个超级英雄不只是你的  也是我的
This thing is as much as mine as it is yours.
我开始觉得只是你的了
Starting to think you think it's all your thing.
比利  但你还是会来的  对吧
Billy, you're still gonna do it, though, right?
好兄弟会怎么做
I mean, what would a good brother do?
各就各位
All hands on deck.
感谢您赐予我们家人  感谢您赐予我们今日
Thank you for this family. Thank you for this day.
感谢您赐予我们食物  抱歉比利没伸手
Thank you for this food. Sorry Billy's hand's on vacay.
费城有大新闻  出现了一个穿戏服的英雄
Big news in Philly. Got a costumed hero.
他做得挺好
He's doing good.
嗯  但真的好吗
Yeah, but is he, though?
有争议  说吧
Controversy. Into it.
跟我们说说你的观点  尤金
Share with us your perspective, Eugene.
说说而已  他都干什么  给人们的手机充电吗
Just saying, he's what? Charging people's phones?
那又怎样  我也能充电  用充电器
So what? I can charge a phone with a plug.
说得好
Preach.
佩德罗  你怎么看
Pedro, any thoughts?
服装太傻了
Costume's stupid.
-是啊  -好吧
- Yeah. - Okay.
白色披风搞得好像他要结婚似的
Big white cape like he's getting married or something.
如果他不能自己选服装呢
What if he didn't get to pick his costume?
你们有想过这点吗
Ever think about that?
你是专家  弗莱迪  你认为呢
You're a specialist, Freddy. What do you think?
弗莱迪  我们从积极的一面来看吧
Yeah, Freddy, let's manage to see the positive.
好吧  我觉得他似乎
Okay, well, I think it looks like
对自己得到的力量没有感激之情
he doesn't have gratitude for what he's been given.
非常详细  好吧
Very specific. All right.
也许对于超级英雄来说
Maybe to the superhero,
感激并不意味着要粘人
gratitude doesn't mean having to be clingy.
粘人  有趣的想法
Clingy? Wow, interesting take.
也许有时超级英雄
You know, maybe sometimes a superhero
只是想要一点私人时间
just wants a little me time.
私人时间也可以解释为
You know, me time could also be construed
把家人推开
as pushing away his family.
家人  他们是家人了吗
Family. Is that what they are now?
这是"超级英雄综合症"的典型症状
It's a classic symptom of "Superhero Syndrome."
这是德国心理学家海因里希·冯·德国某某提出的
Coined by German psychologist Heinrich Von German-something,
他认为超能力会变成吞噬一切的毒品
where superpowers become an all-consuming narcotic.
孩子  我们还没吃完饭
Son, we're still eating dinner.
他需要的是一个跟班
What he needs is a sidekick.
你说说哪有酷跟班
Name one cool sidekick.
达拉  你怎么一直沉默  宝贝
Darla, why are you so quiet over there, baby?
你从来不会无话可说
You're never at a loss for words.
我在吃饭
I'm eating.
我为什么还要来上学
Why am I still doing this?
你不能每天都逃课
Well, you can't skip every day.
你这个年龄当然不行
Not at your age.
但我已经不是这个年龄了
But I'm not your age anymore.
但是我可以跟你一起走
But I can go with you.
我们只需要骗过保安  好吗
We just gotta trick the guard out, you know?
比利  你要去哪儿
Billy, where are you going?
你还是会来和我一起吃午餐的  对吧
You're still gonna have lunch with me, right?
比利
Billy!
活力先生还是会来食堂吃饭的  对吧
Sir Zaps-A-Lot's still gonna eat in the cafeteria, right?
好了
All right.
你有没有看...
Did you check it to...
大家通常会给我一点钱
People typically give me a little money, you know...
你们俩挺甜蜜的  祝你们愉快
You're a sweet couple. You guys have a good day.
-天哪  -玛丽  你没事吧
- Oh, my God. - Mary, are you okay?
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?
我怎么知道你的名字
How do I know your name?
我的其中一项超能力就是猜名字
One of my superpowers is name guessing.
你肯定觉得很奇怪
Which is really weird, I bet.
虽然没有超级力量和超高速那么酷
It's not as cool as super-strength or super-speed,
但是遇到新朋友时  真的很有帮助
but it's really helpful when I meet new people.
你受伤了吗
Are you hurt?
我没事  谢谢你
No, I'm okay. Thank you. Um...
我只是需要想一想
I just need a second to think.
今天真是奇怪的一天
This has been such a weird day.
用我的超级观察力
Using my powers of super-observation,
我看到你手里拿着一封大学寄来的信
I see that you're holding a letter from a college in your hand.
你难过是因为大学没录取你吗
Are you upset because you didn't get in?
大学录取我了
I got in.
看来我的超能力失灵了
Well, now my superpowers are failing me
我很困惑
and I am very confused.
嗯  我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
我也说不清  我知道我应该感到兴奋
I don't know. I know I should be excited
因为这是我的梦想
'cause this is my dream
我为此付出了很多很多努力
and I've worked really, really hard for this,
但我感觉
but it's like...
我也说不清  离开家人一点也不有趣  明白吗
I don't know. Leaving my family does not feel fun, you know?
我能给你一点建议吗
Could I give you a little piece of advice?
不要担心其他人
Don't be worried about everybody else.
永远要为自己着想
Always look out for number one.
这是甘地说的
Gandhi said that.
-他应该没说过  -他说过
- I don't think he said that. - Yeah, he did.
-甘地没说过...  -长得像甘地的人说过
- Gandhi did not say... - Somebody like Gandhi said that.
"永远要为自己着想"
"Take care of number one."
是个很睿智的...可能是尤达说的
It was a really wise... It might've been Yoda.
-听着  -抱歉  不是尤达说的
- Listen. - I'm sorry, no.
我们保留各自的意见吧  关键是做你自己
Agree to disagree. The point is, you do you, you know?
你要为自己着想
You gotta look out for you.
尽量远离这个地方
And get as far away from this place as you can.
我不知道我是否想离开
I don't know if I want to.
你当然想  你打算怎么办
Of course you do. What're you gonna do?
一辈子都住在儿童之家吗
You gonna live in a group home for the rest of your life?
家人是给那些
Look, families are for people
无法照顾自己的人准备的  好吗
who can't take care of themselves, okay? So...
你可以照顾自己
And you can take care of yourself.
还有过马路的时候  要注意来往车辆
Also, look both ways when you cross the street.
我打给他  确认一下
I'll just call him. I'll just make sure.
正在呼叫
It's ringing.
红色旋风  你在忙什么呢
Red Cyclone, hey! Hey, what's going on?
那太疯狂了  顺便说下我是弗莱迪
That's crazy! Yeah, it's Freddy, by the way.
是啊  太疯狂了  那...
Yeah, it's crazy! That is...
太精彩了
Great story.
他没在和任何人讲话
He's not talking to anyone.
我们聊过  聊过的
I was! I was!
我们是朋友  我认识他  真的
We're friends. I know him, I do!
我认识他  我认识他
I know him! I know him! Uh, yeah.
该死
Shit.
开始吧
Come on now.
Eye of the Tiger - Survivor
♪ 手  发出雷霆闪电的手 ♪
♪ Hands! Lightning with my hands! ♪
♪ 发出雷霆闪电的手 ♪
♪ Lightning with my hands! ♪
年轻人
Young man!
你干什么  我正在表演呢
What are you doing? I'm in the middle of a show right now.
你到底有什么事
How can I help you?
我只想感谢你今天过来一起吃午餐
I just wanted to say thank you for showing up to lunch today.
我体验了一把"内裤手提箱"
Yeah, I got a little something called a, uh, suitcase wedgie, right?
我不知道你有没有听说过
I don't know if you've ever heard of it,
这是指有人像这样拎起你的内裤
but it's when someone grabs your underwear like that
像拖着箱子一样走过走廊
and holds you like a suitcase, walks you down the hallway.
这就是我内裤的残骸
And this was my underwear.
恶心
Gross.
你说你会来的
You said you'd come.
是你说我会来  我从来没说过我...
You said I would come! I never said I was...
我是个超级英雄  老兄
I'm a superhero, dude!
你表现得真像个英雄呢
Well, you're acting real heroic.
今天大家给了你多少钱
How much people paying you today?
听着  我现在责任重大  好吗
Listen, I have serious responsibilities now, okay?
但没关系
But that's cool
因为我可以肩负重担  用我的...
because I can carry that burden with my...
♪ 手  发出雷霆闪电的手 ♪
♪ Hands! Lightning with my hands! ♪
9路车  第四街到沃尔纳特街
天啊
Oh, man!
天哪
Holy moly.
别动  大家都别动
Don't move! Nobody move!
不  不
No, no!
不  不  不  稳住  稳住  稳住
No, no, no! Stay, stay! Stay! Stay, stay!
看起来真疼
That looked like it hurts.
是他  是那个超级英雄
It's him! It's that superhero guy!
帮帮我们  救救我们
Help us! Save us!
拜托
Come on!
拜托  有了
Come on... Yeah.
他在干什么  什么情况
What's he doing? What's going on?
不可能
No way.
不  不  拜托不要让我这么做
Oh, no. Oh, no, no. Please don't make me do this.
天啊  这是史上最糟糕的主意
God, this is the worst idea ever!
我做到了  我做到了
I did it! I did it!
我接住了公交车  我接住了公交车
I got the bus! I got the bus.
大家都别动
Nobody move in there.
我得把它放下来  我得把它放下来
I gotta put this thing down. I gotta put this thing down.
不  不  不  狗狗  狗狗  你得走开
No, no, no, no. Doggy, doggy, you have to move.
走开  走开
Move! Move! Shoo! Shoo!
拜托做条乖狗狗  乖狗狗
Please be a good dog, good dog!
你现在是条坏狗狗
You're being a bad dog!
走  走
Go! Go!
拜托走开  拜托走开
Please go. Please move.
太好了  谢谢  谢谢  谢谢
Yes, thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了  不  不
Yeah. Yeah, no, no, no, no.
我刚刚就在附近  所以我想...
I was in the neighborhood, you know, so I thought...
-谢谢  -谢谢
- Thank you! - Thank you!
反正这也算是我的错
You know, it was kind of my fault anyway.
看来费城提前收到了一份圣诞礼物
So, it seems Philadelphia has gotten an early Christmas present
就是属于自己的超级英雄
in the form of its very own superhero.
直播结束
And we're out.
-非常感谢  -不客气
- Thank you very much. - Oh, of course, yeah.
伙计  伙计  伙计  刚刚你看到了吗
Dude! Dude, dude! Dude, did you see that?
看到了  你电击了一辆公交车
Yeah. You electrocuted a bus
差点害死这些人
and almost killed these people.
然后我接住了它
And then I caught it!
弗莱迪  我空手接住了一辆公交车
Freddy, I caught a bus with my bare hands, man!
我接住公交车  就像别人接住球一样
I caught a bus like people catch fly balls.
这是谁做的  是我
Like, who does that? I do that!
比利  你什么也没做
Billy! You do nothing.
你跟人们自拍  让他们给你钱
You take selfies and make people pay you.
算了吧  你这副模样的时候
You know, forget it. I can't really
我真的没办法和你讲话
talk to you when you look like this.
你只是希望能是你
You just wish it was you.
可不是吗
No shit!
你觉得呢  如果能有你的能力我愿意付出一切
You think? I would kill to have what you have.
因为我做的一切都像是
Because everything I do is, like,
为了让别人注意到我的绝望尝试
some desperate attempt to get people to notice me.
为了让别人不要同情我
To not feel sorry for me.
瞧瞧我  瞧瞧我  你真的注意到我了吗
I mean, look at me! Look at me. Do you even see me?
因为大多数人都不会  因为他们不想注意到
'Cause most people don't. 'Cause they don't want to.
现在你也不想注意到了
And now you don't either.
你以为现在这样是真实的你吗
I mean, you think this is who you are?
比利  你才十四岁
I mean, Billy, you're 14,
现在你不比布雷尔兄弟好到哪里去
and now you're no better than the Breyers.
你有这么强大的力量  你却把它
All this power, and all you did
用于卖弄炫耀和欺凌弱小
was turn into a show-off and a bully.
随你怎么说  小鬼
Whatever, kid!
我想做什么就做什么
I do what I want!
而且我大概二十多岁吧
And I'm, like, mid-20s probably!
可能已经三十了
Maybe even, like, 30.
天选之子
Chosen one.
所谓的完美之人
The so-called perfect man.
至纯之心
Pure of heart.
各方面完美无瑕
Flawless in every way.
是什么让你配得上
What made you so worthy?
不好意思  请问有什么...有什么事吗
I'm sorry, can I help... can I help...
你是想要签名什么的吗
Do you want an autograph or something?
把你的能力给我
Give me your power.
否则就去死
Or die.
我去  你是个坏蛋吧
Snap! You're, like, a bad guy, right?
好吧  好吧  在你继续犯傻之前
Okay. Okay, okay, okay. Look, before this gets really stupid for you,
你应该知道我基本上是无敌的
you should know that I'm basically invincible.
凡人的武器伤害不了我们
The weapons of man draw no blood from our kind.
我说了站住别动
I said, stop right there!
唯一能消灭魔法的
The only thing that extinguishes magic...
只有魔法
is magic.
是时候将你的能力转交给我了
Time to transfer your power to me.
你没想到这招吧  是不是  老爷爷
You did not see that one coming, did you, grandpa?
这就叫出阴招
Them's street rules.
好吧  好吧  好吧
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay!
我很抱歉  我很抱歉
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我不应该那样打你的蛋蛋
I never should've punched you in the nuts like that.
那完全是我的错
That was totally my bad.
我们可以谈谈
We can talk about this.
你求饶的样子就像小孩
You grovel like a child.
因为我本来就是小孩
That's because I am one. I'm a kid!
你不想伤害小孩  对吧
You don't wanna hurt a kid, do you?
我相信我会飞  我相信我会飞  我会飞
I believe I can fly! I believe I can fly, I can fly!
弗莱迪说过如果我相信我会飞  我就会飞
Freddy said if I believe I can fly, then I can fly.
所以我相信  我相信  我相信
So I believe! I believe! I believe!
好吧  超人飞翔
Okay. Superman!
超人飞翔  是哪只胳膊来着
Superman! What arm is it?
为什么我飞不起来
Why am I not flying?
拜托  我不想死
Please, I don't wanna die!
我飘起来了
I'm floating!
刚刚怎么回事
What the hell was that?
我会飞
I can fly!
比利
Billy?
弗莱迪  我需要你的帮助
Freddy! I need your help!
你会飞
You can fly?
另一个人是谁
Who's the other guy?
圣诞老人
Santa!
你和圣诞夫人夏天时都做什么
So, like, what do you and Mrs. Claus do in the summertime?
从某种意义上来说
Well, in some ways,
圣诞老人一直都陪着你
Santa is always here for you.
救命  救命  救命
Help! Help! Help!
救救圣诞老人
Help Santa!
圣诞老人需要帮助  救命
Santa needs help! Help!
有需要就叫我们
Give us a shout if you need us.
我要在这里休息一下  如果可以的话
I'm just gonna chill in here for a little while, if that's okay.
太疯狂了
This is crazy.
太疯狂了  你不一定要和这家伙战斗
This is crazy. You don't have to fight this guy.
这不是你的职责  你可以逃跑  对吗
This isn't your job. You can run, right?
对  你可以逃跑  太棒了
Yes, you can run. Awesome!
别过来
Get back!
给我走开
Just get away!
-我是蝙蝠侠  -干掉他  蝙蝠侠
- I'm Batman! - Get him, Batman!
抱歉
Sorry.
收藏版人偶
拜托
Come on!
沙赞
Shazam!
比利
Billy!
比利  你在哪儿
Billy, where are you?
比利
Billy!
你在哪儿  比利
Where are you, Billy?
新的超级英雄拯救费城公交乘客
比利  拜托
Billy, come on!
比利  他在哪儿
Billy. Where is he?
超级反派
Supervillain.
超级反派  超级反派
Supervillain! Supervillain!
更可怕  可怕得多
Worse. Much worse.
变异拟态动物  精神操纵者
Radioactive anthromorph? Psychic energy manipulator?
我不会让你读我的大脑
I won't let you read my mind.
我的大脑一片空白  你进不来
My mind is blank. You can't get in.
我不用读你的大脑
I don't need to read your mind.
因为你会一五一十告诉我
Because you are going to tell me.
他在哪儿
Where is he?
天哪  亲爱的  你没事吧
Oh, my God, honey, are you okay?
-你没事吧  -嗯
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
发生了什么  你受伤了吗
What happened? Are you hurt?
快进来
Come inside.
我们得谈谈
We need to have a talk.
别对他太严厉  好吗
Just don't be so hard on him, okay?
离家出走  撒谎
Running out on us! Lying!
然后我接到学校的电话
Then I get a call from the school,
告诉我你一直在翘课
telling me you've been cutting class!
还打架
Getting in fights!
比尔  这个人救了九个人
Bill, the man saved nine people.
那是不是...
Is that...
费城的神秘英雄  他是谁
我对他的动机存疑
I'm questioning his motive.
弗莱迪怎么和超级英雄在一起
What's Freddy doing with a superhero?
或者说超级英雄怎么和弗莱迪在一起
Or what's a superhero doing with Freddy?
还记得吃晚饭的时候吗
You remember dinner,
比利和弗莱迪争执起来
when Billy and Freddy were arguing
就跟一对老夫妻似的  就像这样
like an old married couple, like this?
救我的时候  他知道我住在儿童之家
When he rescued me, he knew I lived in a group home.
他知道我的名字  他叫我玛丽
He knew my name. He called me Mary.
等等  你是说比利就是人力风暴吗
Wait, are you saying Billy's the Human Power Storm?
是的  你们终于想明白了
Yes! You guys figured it out!
完全靠你们自己  我没帮忙
All on your own. I didn't help.
-我没违背任何承诺  -你早知道吗
- I didn't break any promises. - You knew?
我是个好妹妹
I'm a good sister!
你是怎么想的
I mean, what were you thinking?
然后你还把弗莱迪也牵扯进来
And then you bring Freddy into it.
给他点空间  他有点沮丧  好吗
Give him some space, guys. He's a little upset, okay?
比利
Billy?
你就是他
You're him.
你就是那个英雄
You're the hero.
现在不是了  所以...
Yeah, well, not anymore, so...
我的笔记本怎么在你那儿
Why do you have my notebook?
尤金完成了你的搜寻
Eugene finished your search.
听着  我不是黑客好吗
Look, I'm not a hacker, okay?
但我玩过《看门狗》和《黑客精英》
But I have played Watch Dogs and Uplink.
均为黑客题材游戏
也许我学会了一些技巧  也许我用它们进入了
And maybe I did pick up a few skills, which maybe did get me into
大多数人进不了的联邦数据库  但是...
federal databases most people can't get into, but...
你真厉害  但我要走了
Good for you, but I'm gonna go.
你父母名叫玛丽莲和C·C·巴特森
Your parents' names are Marilyn and C.C. Batson.
什么
What?
你出生在明尼苏达州祖布罗塔
You were born in Zumbrota, Minnesota.
你三岁的时候他们离婚了
They divorced when you were three.
那年你妈妈搬来了这里
Your mom moved here that year.
二十个月之后  你走失了
Twenty months later, you got lost.
你一直没找到他们
You never found them
因为你爸爸在佛罗里达州蹲了十年监狱
'cause your dad's been in prison in Florida for ten years.
而你妈妈...
And your mom's...
怎么了
What?
她死了吗
Is she dead?
她离这里只有两站地铁
She's two subway stops away.
什么
What?
你没找到她
You know, you didn't find her
是因为她改回了娘家的姓
because she reverted to her maiden name.
比利  比利
Billy! Billy!
-维克托  去拿钥匙  -拿了
- Victor, get the keys. - I got it.
孩子们  在这等着  也许比利会回来
Kids, stay here in case Billy comes back.
我是个寄养妈妈  你有什么超能力
来吧  进屋  走吧
Come on. Inside, let's go.
等等  我以为我们要去追比利
Wait. I thought we were running after Billy.
不  我们暂时在这里等着
No, we're gonna wait here for now.
比利
Billy?
弗莱迪
Freddy?
真是古色古香
How quaint.
算了  收回前言
Actually, I take that back.
真是个狗窝
What a shithole.
稍等
Just a second.
我已经上班迟到了  好吗
Hey, look, I'm late for work already, all right?
我们不需要杂志什么的
We don't need any magazines or whatever.
-谢谢  -不  我不是卖杂志的
- Thanks, though. - Oh, I'm not.
你可能认不出我了
You probably don't recognize me...
但我找到回家的路了
but I found my way home.
妈妈
Mom.
是我
It's me.
天哪
Oh, God.
是你吗
Is it?
等一下
Hang on.
门口是谁
Who's at the door?
是...
It's, um...
谁都不是  特拉维斯
It's no one, Travis.
那不是爸爸  对吧
That wasn't Dad, was it?
对
No.
听着
Listen, um...
真的是你啊
It's really you, huh?
我不是故意跑丢的  你明白对吗
I didn't mean to run away. You know that, right?
我没抓住你的手  但那是个意外
I let go, but it was by accident.
嗯  我明白
Yeah, no. I know, yeah.
我看到你了
I saw you.
什么
What?
之后我看到你了
I saw you after.
所以从来都不是你的错
So, it was never your fault.
我那时才17岁  好吗
Look, I was 17, okay?
我爸爸把我赶出来了
And my daddy kicked me out.
而你爸爸完全不想负责任
And your dad just decided not to be a part of anything.
我很痛苦  生活一团糟
And I was hurting, and I was screwed up.
-我想要那只老虎  -我知道
- I want the tiger. - I know.
我知道  亲爱的
I know, honey,
但妈妈并不擅长这个  好吗
but Mom's not exactly going pro here, okay?
比利
Billy?
Billy!
比利
Billy?
老天  比利  这样不好玩
Jesus Christ. Billy, this isn't funny!
来  小朋友
Here you go, buddy.
这样你就能暖和点了  是不是
That should warm you up. Is that better?
当我看到你跟警察在一起的时候
Look, it's just once I saw you with the police,
我意识到他们能比我
I realized that they could do a better job
更好地照顾你
taking care of you than I ever will.
但你过得很好  是不是
But you're good, right?
你已经站稳脚跟了
I mean, you landed on your feet.
因为  你看起来真的很棒
Because, I mean, you look real good.
只是...
It's just...
对我来说  现在时机不对  比尔
now is not a really good time for me, Bill.
我只是想让你知道我过得很好
All I wanted to do is let you know I'm doing good,
但我得回我真正的家了
but I have to get back to my real family.
给
Here.
这是什么
What's this?
玛丽莲  外面怎么回事
Marilyn! What's goin' on out there?
你可能比我更需要它
You might need it more than me.
弗莱迪
弗莱迪  你说得对  抱歉我对你发火了
Freddy, you were right. I'm sorry I yelled at you.
回家吧  比利  回家
Come home, Billy. Come home.
比利  超级反派  超级反派
Billy! Supervillain! Supervillain!
沙赞
Shazam!
你是谁  你想要什么
Who are you? What do you want?
我想要什么
What do I want?
我想要...
I want...
那个
That.
揍扁他  比利
Kick his ass, Billy!
对  比利
Yes, Billy.
那你就试试吧
Try it, by all means.
放他们走我就进去
Let them go and I'll come inside.
不  你先进来
No, first, you come inside,
然后也许我会放他们走
then maybe I'll let them go.
乖孩子
Good boy.
因为你只是个孩子  对吗
Because that's all you are, isn't it?
你多大了
How old are you?
差不多十五岁了
Basically 15.
在我小时候
When I was a child,
那老头跟我说我不够优秀
the old man told me I wasn't good enough.
然而你出现了  一个懦夫
Yet here you are, a coward.
从我手下逃跑  而巫师却选择你
Run from me and the wizard chooses you?
你才不是英雄
You're not a hero.
但我会给你一个成为英雄的机会
But I'm gonna give you the opportunity to be one.
把继承者的力量给我
Give me the power of the champion.
不  别听他的  比利
No. Don't do it, Billy.
把力量交给我  我就放他们走
Give me the power and I'll let them go.
达拉  不
Darla, no.
别走  比利
Don't go, Billy.
-别走  比利  -达拉  过来
- Don't go, Billy. - Darla, come here.
不  我必须去
No, I have to.
好哥哥就会这样做  对吗
It's what a good brother would do. Right?
比利
Billy.
为了来这里  我用了一生的精力
I dedicated my life to getting here.
我掘地三尺
I scoured the earth.
没人相信我
No one believed me.
没人帮助我
No one helped.
没有巫师
Not the wizard.
没有家人
Not my family.
我只有我自己
I only had myself.
我明白
I get it.
我明白那种感觉
I get what that's like.
感觉在这世上孤身一人
Feeling like you're all alone in the world.
站起来
Stand.
感觉有一个东西  只要你能找到它
Feeling like there's that one thing, and if you could just find it,
你就会变得够优秀
then you'd finally be good enough.
站起来
Stand.
继承者的名字
The champion's name.
说出来
Say it.
无意冒犯  先生
Look, no offense, mister,
但我不认为这些东西真的在乎你
but I don't think these things have your best interest at heart.
别听这孩子的话
Don't listen to this child.
拿起权杖
Take the staff.
握住它  说出继承者的名字
Hold it and say the champion's name.
他们在利用你
They're using you.
你得认清这一点  他们在利用你
You have to see that, that they are using you.
说出你的名字
Say your name.
他的名字...
His name...
是火花手指队长
is Captain Sparklefingers.
我们要不断地向你
And we're gonna keep throwing things
又大又丑的独眼脑袋上砸东西
at your big, fat, ugly-eyed head,
直到你放我们的兄弟走
until you let our brother go.
幸好我没把那个蝙蝠镖卖掉
Boy, am I glad I didn't sell that Batarang.
-佩德罗  那是台灯吗  -这灯不好看
- Pedro, is that a lamp? - It's an ugly one.
快  快  快
Come on. Come on. Come on.
你们的好意我心领了
Guys, I appreciate the thought,
真的  但我觉得你们的武器帮不上忙
I really do, but I don't think your weapons are gonna help.
你们可以把它们丢掉了
You can put 'em down now.
刚刚门就在这里
The door was right here.
比利  我们怎么离开这里
Billy, how do we get outta here?
什么  你以为我知道  我不知道
What, you think I know? I don't know.
这边走
This way!
快  快  快  跟着达拉
Go, go, go. Follow Darla.
干得漂亮  达拉  快  快  快
Good job, Darla. Go, go, go!
孩子们
Kids?
这门怎么开着
Why is this open?
弗莱迪  玛丽
Freddy? Mary?
佩德罗  佩德罗  快
Pedro, Pedro, come on.
弗莱迪  弗莱迪  跟上
Freddy? Freddy, keep up.
达拉  在前面带路
Darla, stay in front.
我们得快点
We gotta hurry.
这么多门
So many doors.
总有一扇门能出去  对吗
One of these has to be a way out, right?
是啊  希望如此
Yeah, I would hope so.
不是这扇
Not this one.
好了  不要再开门了
Okay, no more doors.
大家都不要再开门了
Nobody open any more doors.
拜托  比利  我们该怎么办
Come on, Billy. What are we gonna do?
达拉  我不知道
Darla, I don't know.
你肯定知道  努力想一想
Yes, you do. Just think.
你上次怎么出去的
How'd you get out last time?
上次  我在想地铁
Last time, I thought about the subway,
然后就到地铁上了
and I was on the subway.
好的  比利  那就努力想地铁
Okay. Then, Billy, look, think about the subway.
想这里之外的任何地方  好吗
Think about any place except for here, okay?
脱衣舞俱乐部
臀陷酒吧
免费辣鸡翅
快  快  快
Come on, come on, come on.
你为什么要挡住我的眼睛
Why are you covering my eyes?
真的吗  这就是你首先想到的地方
Really? This is the first place you think of? Wow!
不用谢我
You're welcome!
为什么我不能看里面的东西
Why can't I see what's inside?
你不到年龄
You are not old enough.
我够大了  知道那里音乐很棒
Old enough to know that was great music.
我不喜欢
Not my thing.
弗莱迪呢
Where's Freddy?
你也是  辣椒酱
Yeah, you, too, Sriracha.
祝你圣诞快乐
Hey, have a holly jolly Christmas.
弗莱迪  你在做什么
Freddy! What are you doing?
-都是好人  -都是好人
- Nice people. - Nice people?
-拜托  -那是闪粉吗
- Come on. - Is that glitter?
她们有闪粉  我能要点吗
They have glitter! Can I get glitter?
不行  别跟她们要
No, not from them.
求你了
Please?
不行
No.
达拉
Darla.
快  快  快  大家快跑
Go, go, go. Everybody, go!
弗莱迪  弗莱迪  弗莱迪
Freddy? Freddy, Freddy.
一  二  三  上来  我们走
One, two, three. Up, up. Up we go.
冬季嘉年华
嘉年华  快  玛丽  快
Carnival, go! Go, Mary, go.
快  佩德罗  快
Come on, Pedro. Come on.
不要跑  也不要慢慢走  自然就好
Don't run, but don't walk. Just be cool.
自然点  就像孩子们在嘉年华的正常表现
Act naturally, like kids naturally act in a carnival.
-他不会来这里找我们的  -是他吗
- He's not gonna look for us here. - Is that him?
-天哪  -那是美国电长
- Oh, my God! - Dude, it's Zap-tain America!
-力量小子  -他是个模仿者  好吗
- Power Boy! - He's an impersonator, okay?
对  我是个模仿者  我是假冒自己的
Yeah, I'm an impersonator! I'm a fake version of myself.
别拍照片
Don't take pictures.
沙赞
Shazam!
他去哪了
Where'd he go?
他还会隐形吗
What, is he invisible now?
老天  我刚把口水吐到婴儿身上了
Man, I just spit on a baby!
那是什么
Yo, what is that?
那个人是谁
Who is that guy?
继承者
Champion.
你配不上这个名字
You don't deserve that name.
看到那个了吗  上面那个
See that? Look at that up there!
躲在一群即将被你害死的无辜的人身后
Hiding behind innocent people who will now die.
因为内心深处你仍然是个害怕的小男孩
Because deep down you're still just a scared little boy.
不
No.
跑  快跑
Run! Run!
-我们要怎么办  -抓住
- What do we do? - Just hold on!
-抓住什么  -护栏  白痴
- To what? - The bar, you idiot!
你想要我做英雄的
Well, you wanted me to be a hero.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
不行  老家伙在上面
Okay, no. Old guy's up there
身上还有好几个精神实体
harboring multiple spiritual entities.
还有  他跟你有一样的能力
Plus, he has the same powers as you.
还有  他知道自己在做什么
Plus, I mean, he knows what he's doing.
还有  你是我最好的朋友
Plus, I mean, you're my best friend.
我不想你去死
I don't want you to die.
如果超级英雄不能救自己的家人
If a superhero can't save his family,
那他就不算英雄
he's not much of a hero.
这个口头禅还不错
That was a decent catchphrase.
沙赞
Shazam!
现在我们再试一次
Now, let's try this again.
或者再试试这个
Or try that again!
比利  当心
Billy, look out!
激光眼  他有激光眼
Laser eyes! Guys, he's got laser eyes!
可惜你的准头太烂了
Too bad your aim sucks balls!
那是他的力量基质
That's his power matrix.
他的什么
His what-what?
当那些恶魔离开他的眼睛
When the demon guys leave his eye,
他就会失去力量
he loses his powers.
所以蝙蝠镖伤到了他
That's why the Batarang hurt him.
这边
Over here!
等等  你要干什么
Wait. What are you doing?
相信我  分而治之
Trust me. Divide and conquer.
我们把那些恶行和他的眼睛分开
We separate the Sins from the eye,
他就只是个老头
and he's just an old man.
把小杂种们抓起来
Gather the mutts.
快跑
Run!
达拉  不
Darla, no!
给你  拿着
Here. Take it.
拿着  送给你的
Take it. It's for you.
抱紧它
Hold it tight.
闭上眼睛  都会没事的
Close your eyes. Everything's gonna be okay.
好吗
Okay?
好
Okay.
沙赞
Shazam!
游戏时间结束了  小子
Playtime's over, boy.
你的朋友们帮不了你了
Your friends can't help you anymore.
沙赞
Shazam!
把戏不错
Nice trick.
朗朗上口
Catchy.
简单两个字
One simple word.
我的把戏更好
I have a better trick.
四个字
Four words.
杀了女孩
Kill the little girl.
-达拉  不  -杀我吧
- Darla, no! - Take me instead!
住手
Stop!
比利  他眼睛里还有一个恶魔
Billy, there's one more demon guy in his eye!
你得把它从他脸上的洞里扯出来
You gotta just rip it out of his face hole!
那是他力量的来源
It's where he gets his power.
伸手啊
Reach for it.
你敢吗
I dare you.
明智的决定
Wise decision.
把手放在权杖上
Hands on the staff.
比利  别照做  比利
Billy, don't do this. Billy!
-比利  -别照做  比利
- Billy. - Don't do it, Billy!
不要
Don't!
说出我的名字
Say my name
我才能把力量传给你
so my power may flow through you.
我向你敞开心扉  比利·巴特森
I open my heart to you, Billy Batson.
这意味着  我选择你作为继承者
And in so doing, choose you as champion.
用你的心  释放你最强大的力量
With your heart, unlock your greatest power.
我们兄弟姐妹的宝座正在等待
The thrones of our brothers and sisters await.
各就各位
All hands on deck.
说出我的名字
Say my name.
比利
Billy!
不是我的名字  不是
No, not my name. No.
是我一喊就变身成这样的那个名字
Say the name that I say to turn into this guy.
沙赞
Shazam!
各位
Guys.
怎么回事
What's happening?
我会飞
I can fly!
各位
Guys.
瞧瞧这肌肉
Check out these guns.
不  这不可能
No. It's not possible.
哎呀  先生  抱歉我抢了你的拐杖
Gee-whiz, mister. Sorry I took your cane.
你想要回去吗
Do you want it back?
各位  我不相信暴力
Guys, I don't believe in violence,
但我觉得我们应该狠狠揍他一顿
but I think we should kick this guy's butt, like, really hard.
各位  我觉得我能跑得特别
Guys, I think I can move really...
快
fast.
超高速  确认
Hyper-speed! Check!
比利  那只眼睛
Billy! The eye!
当心
Look out!
什么
What?
什么  老兄
What! Dude!
你差点把我炸了
You almost exploded me.
老兄  我研究过每一个
Dude, I've studied the fighting techniques
超级英雄的战斗技巧
of every single superhero.
你有什么本事
What do you got?
好吧  吓死人了
Well, that's terrifying.
游戏玩够了  小子
Enough games, boy.
你以为一群孩子能...
You think a pack of children can...
慢着  什么
Wait, what?
当我慢慢享用你的心脏时
You will beg for mercy
你会向我
as I feast on your heart...
求饶
slow.
你是在做邪恶反派的发言吗
Are you making some big evil guy speech right now or something?
你离我差不多有一英里远
You're, like, a mile away from me right now.
底下车水马龙
There's cars and trucks.
我会让整个世界臣服在我的掌控之下...
I will have the world eating out of the palm of my hand...
我只看到嘴在动  什么也听不到...
All I see is mouth moving. I don't hear any...
只有我有能力释放...
Only I have the power to unleash...
随便吧  去他的
Whatever. Screw it.
天啊  那些人
Oh, my gosh. Those people!
我接住你了
I caught you.
我能行  我能行
I got it. I got it.
天哪  我真能行
Oh, my God. I do got it.
说来你一定不信
You're not gonna believe this,
不过你是我战斗的第一个反派
but you're actually the first villain I've ever fought.
这对我来说可是件大事
It's kind of a huge deal for me.
救命啊
Somebody help!
真的是你
It's really you.
我叫达拉  我今年特别乖
My name is Darla, and I've been really good.
什么
What?
糟糕
Oh, crap.
不不不不不不
No, no, no. No, no. No!
不不不
No! No, no.
天啊
Oh, my God!
他是在内裤手提箱我们吗
Is he giving us suitcase wedgies?
这其实是七宗罪  对吧
So this is, like, the Seven Deadly Sins, right?
我向来不擅长数学
I mean, I've never been great at math,
但那个狂暴的大块头  是暴怒对吧
but, uh, the big, angry one, that's Wrath, yeah?
然后暴食也很明显
And then Gluttony, obvi.
还有傲慢  贪婪  懒惰和色欲
Pride, Greed, Sloth, Lust,
不过说实话  我以为色欲会更性感呢
who I thought was gonna be way hotter, if I'm being honest.
但这才六个  幸运的第七个呢
But that's only six. Where's lucky number seven?
那个小家伙呢  嫉妒在哪儿
Where's little man? Where's Envy?
是因为我和我家人太赞了  他害怕了吗
Is he just scared of me and my family because we're so awesome?
这我能理解
Because I get that.
其他的恶行  他们都能出来战斗
Like, the other sins, they get to come out and fight
因为他们又壮又强又可怕
because they're big and strong and scary.
可是嫉妒...
But Envy...
他只是个小矮子
he's just the runt.
所以其他的恶行从来都不邀请他出来玩  伙计
And that's why all the other sins never invite him out to play, man.
因为他们知道谁会赢
Because they all know who'd win.
赢的一定不会是软弱无能丑陋的嫉妒
And it's not weak, worthless, ugly Envy.
逮到你了
Gotcha.
沙赞
Shazam!
准备好去围捕你的伙伴们了吗
Ready to go round up your buddies?
不  不
No. No!
力量是这样的
Here's the thing about power.
如果无人与你分享  那要力量还有什么用
What good's power, if you got nobody to share it with?
-干得漂亮  -看吧
- Nice. - Ta-da!
-太恶心了  -一击必杀
- That's disgusting. - Fatality.
听我的声音
I got the voice.
说什么
What's that?
我能拥有我想要的一切
I can have anything I've ever wanted?
比利
Billy.
-不不不  -停下
- No, no, no! - Stop it!
-别看那东西  -比利  不要啊
- Don't look at that! - Billy, don't do it!
-你们真该听听自己的反应  -一点都不好笑
- You should hear yourselves! - Not funny.
怎么  你们以为我会把恶魔球塞进脑袋里吗
What, you think I'm gonna put a demon ball in my head?
太恶心了
That's disgusting.
-一点都不好笑  -挺好笑的  骗到我了
- Not funny. - That's pretty funny. You got me going.
-骗到我了  -各位  各位
- You got me going. - Guys, guys.
怎么了
What?
好耶  我们成功了
All right, we did it!
All right, yeah! We did it!
你们都安全了  没有危险了
You guys are all safe. There's no more danger anymore.
我们没事  没事了  好耶  好耶
We're fine. It's okay. All right, all right, all right.
我们没事
We're good.
你确定这样能行吗
You sure this is gonna work?
我就说吧
Told ya.
你们知道这是什么地方吧
You guys know what this place is, right?
一个有恶魔雕像的黑暗阴森的洞穴
A dark, haunted cave with demon statues.
好吧  是的  但也是...
Well, yes, but also...
据点  我们有据点了
Lair! We got a lair!
-据点  -对
- Lair. - Yeah.
你说得对
No, you right.
我们有据点了
We got a lair.
据点是什么
What's a lair?
多亏了六名超级英雄
And thanks to six superheroes,
寒冷费城  冬季嘉年华
市民们安全地回到家中
citizens are back in their homes,
与家人团聚
safe again with their families.
这里有一位目击者描述事件...
And here with an eyewitness account of the events...
太他妈疯狂了  伙计
It was fucking crazy, man!
来自地狱的生物
Creatures from fucking hell!
闪电从每个人的身上冒出来
Lightning coming out of everyone's fucking everything!
太他妈的酷了  伙计
And that is motherfucking cool, man!
成为超级英雄的第一天
So, first day as a superhero.
自动成为史上最佳的一天
Automatic top spot for best ever.
我是打破面条天花板的男人[第一个亚裔英雄]
The man shattered the glass noodle ceiling.
-不  这是种族歧视  -我说就不算是
- No. That's racist. - Not if I say it.
各位
Guys.
各就各位
All hands on deck.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait.
等等
Wait.
感谢您赐予我们食物
Thank you for this food.
感谢您赐予我们今日
Thank you for this day.
感谢您赐予我们家人
Thank you for this family.
也许这次我会留下来
I thought maybe this time I'd stay.
我是说  毕竟
I mean, after all,
我回家了
I'm home.
他最好别坐我们桌
He better not sit at our table.
没戏
Nope!
好吧
Okay.
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
成为英雄  别当恶霸
在等想象中的好朋友出现吗
Waiting for your imaginary BFF to show up?
你们来这干什么
What are you guys doing here?
我们要和你一起吃午餐
Well, we're having lunch with you.
但你们的午餐时间不同
But you guys have different lunch periods.
我们做了一个很特别的安排
Well, we made a very special arrangement.
-达拉  什么情况  -为什么要问我
- Darla, what's going on? - Why are you asking me?
弗莱迪·弗里曼
Freddy Freeman.
这家伙
This guy
教会了我超级英雄需要知道的一切
taught me everything I know about being a dope superhero.
真实故事  你们应该寻求他的指点
True story. You should get some pointers from him.
你怎么样  我全世界最好的朋友
What's going on, my best bud in the whole world?
以及我第一次见到但看起来很酷的孩子们
And also new kids that I'm meeting for the first time but seem very cool?
我邀请了另一位朋友  希望你不介意
I invited another friend. I hope that's okay.
弗莱迪的笔记本
便利店
今日
沙赞自拍
海王自拍
软蛋超人
阿尔弗莱德
毕业舞会
前景不理想
雷霆沙赞！
太阳神
Sun of Ra.
衔尾蛇
Ouroboros.
所罗门之
Solomon's...
结
knot.
不  不
No! No!
原始的符号
Primitive symbols.
你们这些会走会说的猴子和你们的洞穴壁画
You walking, talking monkeys with your cave drawings.
你认为获得魔法只有一种途径
You assume there's only one way to gain magic.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
途径多得超出想象
There are more ways than a mind can imagine.
上帝在上  怎么回事
What in God's name?
上帝得听我的  博士  而不是反过来
I name the gods, Doctor. Not the other way around.
冥思螨  拥有精神控制能力
我们在一起会多开心啊
Oh, what fun we're going to have together.
七界即将成为我们的囊中之物
The Seven Realms are about to be ours.
雷霆沙赞！
别太自责  伙计
Don't beat yourself up, buddy.
你会找到伴侣的
You're gonna find someone.
对  我很确定
Yeah, I'm sure.
因为海里的鱼多了去了[天涯何处无芳草]
Because there's plenty of fish in the sea.
当然不是真的  我不能和鱼说话
Of course it's not real. I can't talk to fish.
和鱼心灵感应交流  测试一
即使我能
Even if I could,
这个能力有什么酷炫的应用吗  说真的
I mean, honestly, what could we do with that that's cool?
不好说  比如指挥一支数十亿的海洋大军呢
I don't know, maybe command an army of billions in the ocean.
对哦  不过也没有很酷炫啦
Oh, yeah. Well, that's not that cool.